我们对结婚是认真的。无论什么。我给你写了张便条说我不能来。
We're serious about getting married. Whatever. I sent you a note to say I couldn't come.
我把它交给艾琳·皮克福德，让她交给你。
I gave it to Eileen Pickford to give to you.
艾琳?
Eileen?
我的母亲吗?是的。
My mother? Yeah.
不，别告诉我你没拿到?
No, don't tell me you didn't get it?
我很……喜欢你。
I'm very... fond of you.
我只是觉得我不能再这样下去了。
I just don't think I can do this any more.
我以涉嫌袭击罪逮捕你。
I'm arresting you on suspicion of assault.
你不能逮捕他!
You're not arresting him!
这是关于你在田野里弯腰
There's summat about you bending over in a field
这让我几乎无法控制自己。
that makes me almost unable to contain myself.
噢!
Ow!
告诉我我爸什么时候去世的。这不是意外。她杀了他。
Tell me about when my dad died. It wasn't an accident. She killed him.
我们决定不买订婚戒指
We decided against an engagement ring,
所以，我们俩买了一辆车。
so instead, we bought a car between us.
朱蒂丝，这是威廉，我的长子。你好。
Judith, this is William, my eldest. Hello.
他在我们家搞过那个婊子。
He's had that bitch in our house.
别再回来了。
Don't come back.
字幕 memoryonsmell http://UKsubtitles.ru.
Subtitles by MemoryOnSmells http://UKsubtitles.ru.
你不能就这样离开他。我不能?
You can't just leave him. Can't I?
为什么不呢?他离开了我。
Why not? He left me.
我是说，你不能把他丢在荒郊野外。
I mean, you can't just abandon him in the middle of nowhere.
你认为我应该让他一次又一次地羞辱我……
You think I should let him humiliate me over and over again...
弯曲!．.假装一切都很好，而实际上
Bend! ..and pretend that everything's fine and dandy, when in actual fact
我快要精神崩溃了?
I'm having a nervous bloody breakdown?
妈妈!
Mum!
哦。
Oh.
你还好吗?
Are you all right?
卡洛琳?
Caroline?
白痴。你是个白痴。
Idiot. You're an idiot.
为什么我是白痴?告诉她。
Why am I an idiot? Telling her.
他可能什么都没做。
He probably wasn't even doing anything.
他恨她。他讨厌朱蒂丝。
He hates her. He hates Judith.
他可能只是想摆脱她。
He was probably just trying to get rid of her.
妈妈。
Mum.
我很抱歉。
I'm sorry.
我不该说的。
I shouldn't have said anything.
他们什么也没做。他们只是喝醉了。
They weren't doing anything. They were just drunk.
他让她进了屋子。
He let her into the house.
他们是否做了什么并不重要。
It doesn't matter whether they were doing anything or not.
重要的是他肤浅，意志薄弱……
What matters is that he's shallow and weak-willed...
我不能相信他
and I can't trust him.
虽然我很想去。
Much as I'd like to.
为了你。
For your sake.
我的缘故。
My sake.
每个人的缘故。
Everyone's sake.
你还好吗，妈妈?
Are you all right, Mum?
是吗?
Are you?
来吧。
Come on.
我找不到停车位。
I couldn't find a parking space.
他们说了什么?
What have they said?
嗯…他们没有提出指控。这只是一个警告。
Um... they're not pressing charges. It is just a caution.
哦。
Oh.
我知道这辆车看起来很奢华。
Here, I know it looks extravagant, the car.
是的，你妈妈可能会喜欢，但我不知道，我…
And, yeah, your mother might have liked one, but I don't know, I...
她从不为车而烦恼。
She were never bothered about cars.
奇数。
Odd.
你说我妈妈没有给你那张纸条。
That thing you said about my mother not giving you that note.
你希望她这么做吗?给你的?
Do you wish she had? Given it to you?
你不能这么想，对吧?
Well, you can't think like that, can you?
没有，但你呢?
No, but do you?
不!当然不是!
No! Course not!
但你不生她的气，因为她没做什么?
But you aren't cross with her, for not doing?
不。
No.
我母亲是个了不起的女人。
She was a fantastic woman, my mother.
是的，她是。你是对的。
Yeah, she were. You're right.
我当然没什么可抱怨的。
I've certainly got no complaints.
尘埃落定。
Done and dusted.
下次，离那个讨厌的小娘们远点。
And next time, give the weedy little twat a wide berth.
你没事吧?
You all right?
是关于什么的?
What were it about?
吉莉安吗?你知道的和我一样多，Robbie。
Gillian? You know as much as me, Robbie.
那个探长说了什么?的东西。
What did he say, the inspector? Stuff.
回头见。正确的。
I'll see you back there. Right.
Paul Jaktri说了什么?
And what was Paul Jaktri saying?
大便。
Shit.
什么鬼东西?我能和我爷爷一起开雷克萨斯吗?
What kind of shit? Can I go in t'Lexus with my grandad?
什么鬼东西?爷爷，我能和你一起去吗?
What kind of shit? Grandad, can I go with you?
你还好吗?对不起，我破坏了你的聚会。
You OK? I'm sorry I spoilt your party.
啊…
Ah...
啊。
Ah.
我要回我的房间了。
I'm going to my room.
我想我最好还是多呆一会儿。你没锁门。
I thought I'd better hang about. You left the door unlocked.
我给西莉亚打个电话，看看她怎么样了。
I'll ring Celia, see if she's all right.
正确的。毫米。
Right. Mm.
如何……事情怎么样，嗯…警察局吗?
How... how were things at the, um... police station?
我不想让你和卡洛琳误会我们的关系。
I'd hate you and Caroline to get the wrong idea about us.
看在我爸爸的份上。
For my dad's sake.
他不是这样的，拉菲。他是个好孩子。
This isn't how he behaves, Raffy. He's a good lad.
我相信他是。
I'm sure he is.
天知道他为什么不能摆脱它。他……他会做得很正常。
God knows why he couldn't rise above it. He... he would do normally.
的孩子。好吧，男孩们，不管怎样。
Kids. Well, boys, anyway.
我…我自己吃。好。
I...I helped myself. Good.
我希望那是…绝对好。
I hope that's... Absolutely fine.
抱歉……怎么啦？
Sorry about... What?
哦，公共场合的家丑。我和卡洛琳。
Oh, dirty linen in public. Me and Caroline.
嘿,听。别跟我道歉。
Hey, listen. Don't apologise to me.
没有任何理由。我不评判别人。
Not for anything. I don't judge people.
从来没有。人生苦短。
Never have done. Life's too short.
让我们坦率地说。
Let's be frank.
我们都不完美。讽刺的是……
We're none of us perfect. The ironic thing is...
怎么啦？哦。
What? Oh.
我有这个…
I had this...
扔东西,
fling thing,
affair-fest,
这个朱蒂丝的尴尬错误
embarrassing mistake thing with this Judith,
四个……三个月前。
four... three months ago.
我无聊的时候告诉我。
Tell me when I get boring.
重点是她…
Oh, the point is she...
我一个人在屋里。我们的家，我和卡罗琳的家。
I was in the house by myself. Our house, mine and Caroline's.
然后她出现了。朱迪思。
And she turns up. Judith.
我也甩不掉她。威廉很早就放学回家了，
And I can't get rid of her. William comes home from school early,
因为他的高级水平考试才考到一半。
because he's in the middle of his A levels.
他以为我们在做什么。
He assumes we're up to stuff.
但我们不是。绝对不是。到处都是。
Which we're not. Absolutely not. All over.
过去的事了。大错特错。
Thing of the past. Big, bad mistake.
非常感激能回到光荣，高傲，疯狂的卡罗琳身边，
Desperately grateful to be back with glorious, snotty, mad Caroline,
虽然是在空卧室里。
albeit in the spare bedroom.
可现在她又疯了，说我又疯了。
But now she's gone all berserk and says I'm out on my ear again.
大便。
Shit.
我已经……
I've...
我得上楼去看看拉菲怎么样了。
just got to pop upstairs and see if Raffy's OK.
确定。
Sure.
拉夫?
Raff?
我想知道保罗说了什么让你这么生气。
I want to know what Paul was saying that made you so cross.
他是个白痴。我不能说我会和你争论这个问题。
He's an idiot. Well, I can't say I'd argue with you over that.
你也是个白痴。
And you're an idiot as well.
车怎么样了?粉碎。
How's the car? Smashing.
你不能开车送我去最近的火车站吗?
You couldn't drive me to the nearest railway?
你要去哪里?哈罗盖特。
Well, where are you heading? Well, Harrogate.
我开车送你去。我要去看西莉亚。她几乎没见过那辆车。
Well, I'll drive you there. I'm off over to see Celia. She's barely seen that car.
但必须是明天早上。
But it'll have to be tomorrow morning.
我现在不走!
I'm not setting off now!
它是黑暗的。很好。太好了。是…?
It's dark. Fine. Great. Is that...?
所以…我能留下吗?
So... so could I stay?
他能留下来吗?
Can he stay?
艾伦很好心地让我明天早上搭车回哈罗盖特。课程。
Alan's very kindly offered me a lift back to Harrogate tomorrow morning. Course.
如果你……我会很感激的。你不再喝酒了。
Only I'd be grateful if you... you didn't drink any more.
我不希望西莉亚还没坐进车里你就吐了。
I don't want you throwing up in t'car before Celia's even sat in it.
西莉亚还好吧?
Celia all right?
我想她会想去我车里转转的。
Well, I think she'd have liked a turn in t'car.
也许我应该打电话叫辆出租车。别傻了。你待在原地。哦，我去把水壶烧上。
Perhaps I should phone for that taxi. Don't be daft. You stay put. Oh, I'll go and put t'kettle on.
你更想维护自己，你确实想。
You want to stick up for yourself more, you do.
我吗?是的。
Me? Yeah.
你知道，如果你不做什么，
You know, if you weren't doing owt,
如果你真的没有和这个朱蒂丝做什么
if you genuinely weren't doing owt with this Judith...
为什么要接受被开除?
why accept being chucked out?
大概房子的一半都是你的。
And presumably half the house is yours.
早上好,每个人!
Morning, everyone!
爸爸回来了!爸爸回来了!
Daddy's back! Daddy's home!
♬爱的孩子们
♪ Allons enfants de la Patrie
♬你的荣耀终将到来!♪
♪ Le jour de gloire est arrive! ♪
早餐!我做饭!
Breakfast! I'm cooking!
谁想吃煎饼?
Who wants pancakes?
早上好!差十分八点。
Morning! It's ten to eight.
是的,我……对不起，我迟到了。
Yes, I... Sorry I'm late.
哦!
Oh!
“星期天早晨的礼拜仪式来自圣詹姆斯大帝教堂……”
'The Sunday morning service comes from the church of St James the Great...'
哦，滚开。
Oh, piss off.
Pa-pa-pa pom !
Pa-pa-pa pom!
你相信上帝吗?
Do you believe in God?
我过去常常……相信。
I used to... to believe.
1970年代中后期。
Mid-to-late 1970s.
70年代中后期发生了什么?
What happened in the mid-to-late 1970s?
我不确定。
I'm not sure.
但是,呃…从那时起，我们似乎就不去了。为什么?
But, er... that's when we just seemed to stop going. Why?
我想我更愿意在教堂结婚，而不是在婚姻登记处结婚。
I think I'd like to get married in a church rather than a registry office...
在反思。
on reflection.
是谁在制造噪音?好吧，我们可以。
Who's that making that din? Well, we can do.
我…我不认为这是必须的，
I...I don't think it's obligatory these days,
相信上帝，只是因为你想在教堂结婚。
to believe in God, just cos you want to get wed in church.
你到底在搞什么鬼!早上好,亲爱的。
What the hell on earth do you think you're doing?! Morning, darling.
别把我拉屎了，亲爱的!如厕的嘴。
Don't you shitting well "darling" me! Potty mouth.
你在干什么?早餐。想要一些吗?
What are you doing? Breakfast. Want some?
是约翰吗?她让他进来了吗?
Is that John? Has she let him in?
我住在这里!他是怎么回来的?
I live here! How has he got back?
不，你不住在这里，因为你是个混蛋，我把你赶出去了!
No, you don't live here, because I chucked you out for being an arsehole!
是的,嗯…
Yes, well...
这房子有一半是我的!
half this house is mine!
我没有做错任何事!她来了!
I wasn't doing anything wrong! She turned up!
威廉夸张!克服它!别碰那个!
William exaggerated! Get over it! Don't you touch that!
下次你妈再扇我耳光，
And next time your mother slaps me,
你告诉她我会立马还给她一巴掌!困难!
you tell her I will slap her right back! Harder!
你不能把我的厨房弄得一团糟!
You are not making a mess in my kitchen!
这是正确的!我把厨房弄得一团糟!
That's right! I'm making a mess in my kitchen!
当你和那个婊子上床的时候你就丧失了任何权利!
You forfeited any right to anything when you went off shagging that whore!
再大声点，卡罗琳!
Shout a little bit louder, Caroline!
这一点都不好笑!不。
It's not funny! No.
道德上，我不能和你争论。然而，在法律上，更多的妥协!
Morally, I can't argue with you. Legally, however, a tad more compromise!
我不想你在这儿!
I do not want you here!
我不介意你在这里。又不是没有地方了，对吧?
Well, I don't mind you being here. It isn't like there isn't room, is it?
所以，如果你不能对我彬彬有礼，
So, if you can't be civil to me,
滚到另一个房间去，好吗?
just bugger off into another room, all right?
因为如果你要变得难以相处和不合作，
Because if you're going to be difficult and unco-operative,
我可能会把你的东西都扔掉，好吗?
I might just chuck all your things out, OK?
发生什么事情了?
What's happening?
什么都没有。
Nothing.
你爸爸表现得像只猪!
Your father's behaving like a pig!
哦,该死的。她关上了窗户。
Oh, damn. She's shut the window.
你看，我没有表现得像只猪。我愿意完全讲理。
You see, I'm not behaving like a pig. I'm willing to be entirely reasonable.
你在做早餐吗，冰棒?是的，我是。酷。
You're doing breakfast, Popsicle? Yes, I am. Cool.
这一点都不好笑!
It's not funny!
嘿!
Hey!
你想不想开车去巴克斯通岭?
How do you fancy driving over to Buckstones Ridge?
哦……
Oh...
我要去上班了。
I'm just off to work.
拉夫。
Raff.
啊。
Ah.
你对我们的拉夫说了什么?
What have you been saying to our Raff?
冷静点，吉莉安。然后去报警?
Oh, steady on, Gillian. And going to the police?
什么样的人会被16岁的孩子打了还去报警?
What kind of bloke gets beaten up by a 16-year-old and goes whining to the police?
那就说"谢谢你，保罗，没有起诉我"怎么样?
How about, "Thank you, Paul, for not pressing charges"?
你对他说了什么?
What did you say to him?
“谢谢你，保罗，你给了他一个警告。”
"Thank you, Paul, for letting him get off with a caution."
公牛。我只是…你知道的。
Nowt. I were just, like... You know.
怎么啦？
What?
我正说你是个好女人呢。
I were just saying what a fine woman you was.
你这个白痴。任何时候，爱。
You idiot. Any time, love.
反正他也不相信你。哈哈。
Well, he didn't believe you, anyway. Ha-ha.
不，他说了。
Nah, he did.
一开始就不是了，厚脸皮的蠢货。
Not to start with, cheeky git.
直到我描述了你窗户上方潮湿的墙纸都在剥落。
Not till I described the way your wallpaper's peeling off above t'window where it's damp.
还有你那双价值五百万的鞋子。
And your five million pair of shoes.
他床边的那张照片是他，他的叔叔Robbie和他的爸爸。
And that photo he has by his bed of him, his Uncle Robbie and his dad.
是啊，我想他那时才意识到
Yeah, yeah, I think that's when he realised
我真的去过你的楼上。
I really had been in your upstairs.
他疯了。Lickle混蛋。
He went mad. Lickle bastard.
这是……
That's...
喂?吉莉安吗?
Hello? Gillian?
是吗?我是约翰·艾略特。
Yeah? It's John Elliot.
卡洛琳的丈夫。
Caroline's husband.
哦。
Oh.
约翰。
John.
你好。
Hello.
我打电话是想谢谢你昨晚收留我。
I'm just ringing to say thank you for putting me up last night.
噢,那是……
Oh, that's...
我为自己辩护，然后…嗯，她不喜欢。
I stuck up for myself, and, er... well, she didn't like it.
毫不奇怪。
Not surprisingly.
但我做到了。
But I did it.
他在跟人说话。
He's talking to someone.
“谁?”我不知道。他傻笑。
'Who?' I've got no idea. He's smirking.
可能是她，朱蒂丝。
It's probably her, Judith.
我不知道，卡洛琳对不起，我惹你生气了。
Well, I've no idea, Caroline. I'm sorry I upset you.
对不起，我没听你的。你是对的。他是个绝对的……
I'm sorry I didn't listen to you. You were right. He's an absolute...
混蛋。我度过了人生中最美好的时光
jerk. I've spent the best years of my life
嫁给了一个不靠谱，肤浅的…
married to an unreliable, shallow-minded...
以自我为中心…
self-centred...
混蛋。
jerk.
是的。
Yes.
我该怎么办呢?
What am I going to do?
跟他离婚，这次别光说说而已。
Divorce him, and not just talk about it this time.
卖掉房子，平分所有财产。重新开始。
Sell the house, split everything. Start again.
我不能卖这房子!“为什么?”
I can't sell this house! 'Why?'
因为我……我为此付出了很多。我为此付出了那么多努力。
Because I... I've put so much into it. I've worked so hard for it.
它是完美的。我不想卖……
It's perfect. I don't want to sell...
不管怎样，我不能，因为我妈妈……
Anyway, I can't, because my mother...
事实上，我妈妈可能要搬出去了，因为她要结婚了。
Actually, my mother's probably going to move out, because she's getting married.
你的母亲吗?是的。
Your mother? Yes.
你妈妈要结婚了?谁来?
Your mother is getting married? Who to?
哦，只是…
Oh, it's just...
多么甜蜜。
How sweet.
你想让我过去吗?
Would you like me to come round?
“你想去散散步吗?”你想做点什么吗?”
'Would you like to go for a walk? Would you like to do something?'
可能是我说得太多了……
Me going on about stuff a bit too much, probably...
你住的地方真是世界上最美丽的地方。
That's such a beautiful part of the world that you live in.
约翰?约翰,约翰。
John? John, John.
我…我很抱歉。我得走了，因为我在工作。
I'm... I'm sorry. I've got to go, cos I'm at work.
哦，对不起。是的,不…没有问题。
Oh, I'm sorry. Yeah, no... no problem.
那么,再见。我变得抒情起来。
Ta-ta, then. Me waxing lyrical.
是的。哦。再见!
Yeah. Aw. Bye!
也许什么时候能再见到你。是的,是的。
Probably see you again some time anyway. Yeah, yep.
再见。再见。再见。
Bye. Bye-bye. Bye.
可爱的外来生物。
Sweet exotic creature.
“那么，2点怎么样?”
'So, 2 o'clock, then?'
耶稣基督。
Jesus Christ.
他点燃了一支香烟。“那很……”
He's lit a cigarette. 'Is that very...'
这有多糟糕?
How bad is that?
我们不抽烟。
We don't smoke.
哦。啊。
Oh. Ah.
他在早上11点15分喝威士忌。
And he's drinking whisky at quarter-past 11 in the morning.
他在听…该死的弓箭手!
And he's listening to the... bloody Archers!
我得走了。
I've got to go.
好吧，那我们……
Right, well, I'll see you at...
你这个傻婊子!
You silly bitch!
你觉得你给孩子们树立了什么样的榜样?
What kind of example do you think you set these boys, hm?
吸烟!喝酒和私通!
Smoking! And drinking and fornicating!
在那里打滚，就像…放纵的傻帽!
And wallowing there like some... self-indulgent tosser!
你怎么敢这么做?我不想你在这儿!
How dare you do that? I do not want you here!
嗯，运气不好。我住在这里，如果我想抽烟，想带女人来，那我就带!
Well, bad luck. I live here, and if I want to smoke and bring women here, then I'll bring them!
但我不想带女人来这里!
But I don't want to bring women here!
因为我想让我们的婚姻继续下去!
Because I want our marriage to work!
你这个疯子!这段婚姻结束了!
You mad cow! This marriage is over!
它死了!这是多余的!它……从来没有!
It is dead! It is redundant! It... it never was!
我不想再浪费生命中的一秒
And I do not want to waste another second of my life
假装它是值得拯救的东西!
pretending it's something worth saving!
♬你怀里的静电
♪ The static from your arms
♬它是一种催化剂
♪ It is a catalyst
♬你是一种燃烧的化学物质
♪ You're a chemical that burns
♬没有什么比这更好的了。♪
♪ There is nothing like this. ♪
如果几周前有人告诉我的话
If anybody had told me a few weeks ago
我会坐在巴克斯通岭
that I'd be sitting up at Buckstones Ridge,
和一个不是我丈夫的男人牵手，
holding hands with a man who isn't my husband,
他开着他的雷克萨斯开车送我过来
and who's just driven me here in his Lexus,
我还以为他们在跟我开玩笑呢。
I'd have thought they were pulling my leg.
我也不会坐在任何地方
Not that I'd have ever sat anywhere
和我的丈夫手牵手。
holding hands with a man who was my husband.
肯尼斯不是那种乐于助人的人。
Kenneth wasn't the hand-holding sort.
我是说，在麻烦出现之前，
I mean, even before the trouble,
我不认为他有浪漫的天性。
I don't think he'd a romantic bone in his body.
后来，当我发现他是个多么好色的家伙时，嗯……
And then after, when I'd found out what a randy sod he'd been, well...
把锡盖放在任何一种…任何类似浪漫的东西。
that put the tin lid on any sort of... Anything resembling romantic.
我是说，我不再和他交往了。
I mean, I stopped going anywhere with him socially.
我是说，他不知道谁知道谁不知道。
I mean, he didn't know who knew and who didn't.
我的工作原则是做最坏的打算永远是明智的。
And I work on the principle it's always wise to assume the worst.
我是说，这样不好，对吧?
I mean, it's not nice, is it?
大家互相推搡，说:“哦，是她。
Folk nudging each other, going, "Ooh, that's her
她丈夫背着她干这事。
"whose husband's at it with all and sundry behind her back.
“我不知道她是否知道，可怜的婊子。
"I wonder if she knows, poor bitch.
“我想知道她没做什么，让他把目光投向别处。”
"I wonder what she's not doing that's making him look elsewhere."
所以，你进去了。你不出去。
So, you stop in. You don't go out.
你的世界变得越来越小。
And your world gets smaller.
我应该和他离婚的。
I should have divorced him.
但说起来容易，有个孩子要抚养
But it's easy to say, with a child to bring up
而且没有自己的钱。你看，我没有工作。
and no money of your own. And you see, I'd not worked.
我没有事业。
I had no career.
卡洛琳出生时我就放弃了工作。
I'd given up my job when Caroline was born.
在那个时代，女人是这样做的。
Women did in them days.
有一次可能会杀了他。
Could have killed him one time.
我是说，真的，我可以!
I mean, literally, I could have!
他正在装饰厨房。
He was decorating the kitchen.
把天花板漆成一个小梯子。
Painting the ceiling up a little stepladder.
他对自己动手做任何事都一窍不通。
He was hopeless at anything to do with DIY.
总之，他滑倒了，撞到了头。
Anyway, he slipped and banged his head.
他一定是出去了……不会超过一两秒钟的。
He must have been out for... oh, well, no more than a second or two.
当然，我慌了。
But of course, I panicked.
直到他醒过来。
Till he came to.
直到后来我才意识到我的反应太慢了。
It was only afterwards I realised I'd been slow.
我决定，如果这种事再发生，我就在他脸上塞个垫子
And I decided if it ever happened again I'd slip a cushion over his face
然后让他窒息。
and suffocate him.
我吓到你了吗?
Have I shocked you?
不。
No.
哦,上帝。
Oh, God.
很抱歉我一直在说他。
I'm sorry I go on about him.
不，不，不。我只是很抱歉你…你必须经历这一切。
No, no, no, no. I'm just sorry you... you had it to go through.
我告诉你这些只是想让你知道你要娶的是一个什么样的女人。
I'm only telling you this so you know what sort of a woman you're marrying.
你想去酒吧喝一杯吗?
Do you fancy a pint in a pub?
我在想……哦,啊?
I was thinking... Oh, aye?
你今晚为何不在哈罗盖特停留?
Why don't you stop tonight in Harrogate?
哦，我没有什么不愉快的意思。
Oh, I don't mean anything untoward.
我有一间空房。
I've got a spare room.
不过不然的话，带我回哈罗盖特对你来说会是一段漫长的旅程
Only it's going to be a long haul for you otherwise, taking me back to Harrogate
然后出发去哈利法克斯。
then setting off to Halifax.
你今天天刚亮就起床了。
And you were up at the crack of dawn this morning.
我得买把牙刷。
I'd have to buy a toothbrush.
拉夫?
Raff?
Raffy吗?
Raffy?
回答。
Answer it.
“我不能接你的电话。请留言，我会给你回电话的。”
'I can't take your call. Leave a message and I'll ring you back.'
拉夫，是我。
Raff, it's me.
你在哪里?打电话给我或者…或者给我发短信。
Where are you? Just ring me or... or text me.
我…我要知道你在哪里。
I...I need to know where you are.
如果我让你不高兴了，我很抱歉。我知道我让你不高兴了。
I'm sorry if I've upset you. I know I've upset you.
但我得知道你没事。
But I need to know that you're all right.
哦,狗屎。
Oh, shit.
吉莉安吗?拉夫和你在一起吗?
Gillian? Is Raff with you?
是的。
He is, yeah.
他还好吗?
Is he all right?
是的，他很好。
Yeah, he's absolutely fine.
他说了什么?什么都没有。
What's he said? Nothing.
我能跟他谈谈吗?他现在有点忙。他在玩Xbox。
Well, can I talk to him? He's a bit busy at the minute. He's on the Xbox.
是吗?把他从床上弄下来…
Yeah? Well, get him off the f...
坦白说，我觉得他不会想和你谈的。我不知道发生了什么
And to be frank I don't think he'd want to talk with you. I don't know what's happened,
除了他和那个白痴打架，但我想肯定有事发生了。
other than him fighting with that dickhead, but I assume something has.
我猜他终于明白了你是一个多么疯狂的婊子，
I assume that he's finally seen the light and worked out what a mad bitch you are,
所以，如果他想搬来住，我没意见。
so you know, if he wants to move in here, that's fine by me.
我不会强行把他关在这里。你竟敢向他灌输我的坏话。
I'm not keeping him here by force. Don't you dare fill his head with rubbish about me.
那么，就这些了吗?你让他给我打电话!
Will that be everything, then? You just tell him to ring me!
喂?约翰?
Hello? John?
是吗?吉莉安。
Yeah? It's Gillian.
艾伦的女儿。
Alan's daughter.
吉莉安。
Gillian.
对不起，我今天早上不得不挂断电话。
Sorry I had to ring off this morning.
只有老板紧盯着我，而且……
Only the boss were breathing down my neck and...
不，不，那是……我没多想。
No, no, that's... I thought nothing of it.
好,好。
Good, good.
好。事情进展如何?
Good. So, how's things progressing?
她在花园里开了个小集会
Oh, she's having a little coven in the garden
和一个和她一起工作的无聊的小女巫。
with some insipid little witch that she works with.
好了。
Nice.
劳伦斯说她是女同性恋。天知道卡洛琳为什么邀请她来。
Lawrence says she's a lesbian. God knows why Caroline's invited her here.
你知道你昨晚说了什么
You know what you said last night
关于你和这个…
about you having this affair with this...
朱迪思?
Judith?
是吗?嗯…
Yeah? Well...
我也做过类似的事情……
I did something similar and...
你做了吗?是的,…
You did? Yeah, a...
愚蠢，愚蠢的事情。
stupid, stupid thing.
拉夫发现了，所以才会吵起来，
And Raff's found out, and that's what that fight was about,
他去跟罗比住了
and he's gone to live with Robbie.
那是他的叔叔，警察。
That's his uncle, the policeman.
他是个十足的混蛋……
And he's a right bastard and...
胡说!
Bollocks!
我和理查德离婚的时候也是这样。
It was exactly the same when me and Richard got divorced.
我们都没钱买下对方的股份
Neither of us could afford to buy the other one out
所以我们不得不卖掉所有的东西。
so we had to sell up, split everything.
就在中间。我们的房子很漂亮。
Right down the middle. Beautiful house we had.
这让人心碎。
It was heartbreaking.
但你会找到前进的道路。
But you find a way forward.
我得去找个合适的法律顾问。
I'm going to have to get proper legal advice.
是的,很明显。我不知道我在说什么。
Yes, obviously. I don't know what I'm talking about.
你不?我是在讽刺你。我只是说我也经历过同样的事情，
Don't you? I was being sarcastic. I just said I've been through exactly the same thing,
但是，是的，你应该得到适当的法律建议。你为什么这么无礼?为什么?
but, yes, you should get proper legal advice. Why are you being so snippy? Why?
怎么啦？
What?
我爸爸得了老年痴呆症。你知道吗?
My dad's got Alzheimer's. Did you know that?
天啊，我很抱歉。
God, I'm so sorry.
关于我，你不知道的事太多了，卡洛琳
There's a million and one things you don't know about me, Caroline...
因为你从不开口，我也尽量不给别人添麻烦
cos you never ask, and I try not to inflict things on people
除非我觉得他们真的感兴趣
unless I think they're actually interested,
但我从来没觉得你是
but I've never really had the impression that you were,
但你却想当然地认为我会对你感兴趣。
but you just take it for granted that I'll be interested in you.
你不?是你主动提出要过来的。
Don't you? You offered to come round.
但是你给我打电话了。
Mm, but you rang me up.
在你甩了我之后。嘘。
After you'd dumped me. Shh.
你给我打电话希望我能同情你，我确实同情你。
You rang me up expecting me to be sympathetic, which I am.
那对我也没什么好处。然后你就像个男人了。
Not that it'll do me any good. And then you're like a man.
你就这么决定了，我都不知道
You just make this decision that I haven't got a clue
我在说什么，尽管我也经历过。
what I'm talking about even though I've been through it.
我觉得你反应过度了。你在阅读……然后上周又来找我
I think you're overreacting. You're reading things... And then having a go at me last week
在我为所发生的事难过的时候告诉别人
for talking to someone when I was upset about what had happened.
一个有同情心和兴趣的人。
Someone who was sympathetic and interested.
迈克尔·多布森?他试图勒索我。
Michael bloody Dobson? He tried to blackmail me.
他没有。你最好走吧。
He didn't. You'd better go.
我被解雇了吗?
Am I being dismissed?
我不应该给你打电话。对不起，我说了。
I shouldn't have rang you up. I'm sorry I did.
别这么说。
Don't say that.
我只是想让你明白…
I just want you to understand...
你对我的影响。
the effect you have on me.
如果你给我打电话，我就跑过来，尽管我知道你对我并不是真的感兴趣。
If you ring me, I'll run round here, even though I know you're not really interested in me.
我不是…对你不感兴趣。
I'm not... not interested in you.
我…
I'm...
我不知道我是什么。我…
I don't know what I am. I...
你说得对，我从没问过你的事，
You're right, I've never asked you anything about you,
不是因为我不…
and it's not because I don't...
那是因为我自私，没有希望……
It's because I'm selfish and hopeless...
你一直是我的好朋友，而我不知道该怎么做一个好朋友。
and you've been a really good friend, and I don't know how to be a good friend.
在任何人身上。
To anyone.
我父母合不来。
My parents never got on.
我和这些人在自己的房子里长大
I grew up in a house on my own with these people
除非万不得已，他们从不说话，
who never spoke to each other unless they had to,
我以为这很正常
and I thought that was normal.
现在她遇到了一个叫艾伦的家伙，他是个好人，
And now she's met this bloke, this Alan, and he's a sweet man,
他把她看得很重，她也把他看得很重，
and he thinks the world of her, and she thinks the world of him,
她是如此的与众不同!
and she's so different!
我忍不住想知道她是否爱上了我爸爸
And I can't help wondering if she'd been in love with my dad
他曾经爱过她……
and he'd been in love with her...
事情会变得多么不同。
how different things would have been.
我不知道正常的关系是什么样的。
I don't know what normal relationships are like.
我看到了，但我不知道怎么做。
I see them, but I don't know how to do them.
所以我很抱歉。
So I'm sorry.
如果我伤害了你或者不把你当回事，我很抱歉。
I'm sorry if I've hurt you or taken you for granted.
我将尽力不那样做……
I will endeavour not to do that...
在未来。
in the future.
因为我很珍惜你的友谊
Because I do value your friendship and...
我很抱歉，如果我从来没有说清楚或做过什么…
I'm sorry if I've never said or made that clear or done what...
正常人都是这样做的。
normal people do to express these things.
我很抱歉。
So, I'm sorry.
谢谢你！
Thank you.
我觉得你该让自己休息一下，吉莉安，真的。
I think you've got to give yourself a break, Gillian, I really do.
他16岁了。给他一个星期的时间。
He's 16 years old. Give him a week.
让他用Robbie的微波炉煮一个星期。
Give him a week with Robbie's microwave cooking.
给罗比一周时间，让他和一个该死的少年待在家里。你是对的。
Give Robbie a week with a bloody teenager in the house. You're right.
你知道他在哪儿。你知道他很安全。好吧，他受了惊吓。
You know where he is. You know he's safe. OK, he's had a shock.
他发现他妈妈有性行为了。克服它吧。
He's found out his mother has sex. Get over it.
我知道，我知道。这就是生活，你知道吗?
I know, I know. It's just life, you know?
他必须意识到你…
And he has to realise that you have...
你知道，就像其他人一样，
you know, just like everyone else does,
冲动,感情,
urges, feelings,
等他长大了，他会明白的。
and when he's an adult, he'll get it.
他不会回头看你，对你评头论足。
He will not look back on you and make judgments.
他只是需要一点时间。退后，吉莉安。
He just needs a little bit of time. Step back from it, Gillian.
我知道这不容易。
I know it's not easy.
他是你的孩子，但是，
He's your boy, but,
如果你能……是的,是的。
if you can... Yeah, yeah.
是的，你说得对，你说得对。
Yeah, you're right, you're right.
哦,孩子。
Oh, kids.
天啊。
Gosh.
花园里的事情怎么样了?
So, how's things in the garden?
哦，差不多一样。
Oh, much the same.
哦,上帝!
Oh, God!
保罗。耶稣。
Paul. Jesus.
发生了什么事?保罗?怎么啦？
What's happened? Paul? What?
这是谁干的?
Who did this?
谁干的?是拉夫吗?
Who did it? Was it Raff?
罗比吗?
Robbie?
好的。来吧。
OK. Come on.
我带你进去。
Let's get you inside.
我觉得我们应该带你去见皇家公主。
I think we should get you up to the Princess Royal.
我会没事的。
I'll be all right.
发生了什么事?
What happened?
达伦和加文。
Darren and Gavin.
海莉的兄弟们发现了我和你在一起
Hayley's brothers found out I'd been at it with you
所以他们和几个大混蛋打了我。
so them and a couple of big bastards laid into me.
所以,我……我想订婚取消了，是吧?
So, I... I guess the engagement's off, eh?!
你这个肮脏的家伙。
You dirty sod.
他们说要往我身上倒汽油，然后把我点着。
They said they was going to pour petrol over me and set me on fire.
我相信了他们。
I believed them.
让奶奶进来。
Let Granny in.
谢谢。
Thanks.
早上好!嗨。
Morning! Hi.
只是想让你知道…哦，你真聪明。
Just to let you know... Oh, you're very smart.
我和艾伦要去哈利法克斯
Me and Alan are popping over to Halifax
去看看可能的婚礼地点。
to look at possible venues for the wedding.
所以我今晚不会来了。我要和艾伦一起去吉莉安家。
So I won't be here this evening. I'll be stopping over at Gillian's with Alan.
正确的。
Right.
很抱歉这么早过来，但你要去上班，所以……
I'm sorry to pop over so early but you'll be going to work so...
刷牙。我的鞋子在哪里?
Brush your teeth. Where are my shoes?
不管你把它们放在哪里。
Wherever you left them.
他很紧张。他拿到了他的第一篇英语论文。
He's very nervous. He's got his first English paper.
他昨晚来过，艾伦。
He stopped over last night, Alan.
是的，我猜想。我,嗯…看到那辆车了。
Yes, I assumed. I, um... saw the car.
他本来打算睡在空卧室的，但是……
He was going to sleep in the spare bedroom but...
我不知道，一件事接着一件事，
I don't know, one thing led to another,
我有一张双人床，我们要结婚了，所以……
and I've got a double bed and we are getting married so...
我们睡在一张床上。
we shared the same bed.
好的。
OK.
我不知道人们会怎么想。
I don't know what people'll think.
对你有好处。我只是想，“这是怎么回事?”
Well, good for you. I just thought, "What the hell?"
什么人?
What people?
我也不在乎任何人。
I don't care. Anyone.
正确的。
Right.
就像我说的，我们又不是不结婚，因为我们已经结婚了，所以…
As I say, it's not as though we're not getting married, cos we are, so...
所以呢?
So?
你不介意吧?我吗?不。
You don't mind? Me? No.
不，当然不是。
No, of course not.
所以…太棒了。
So... It's great.
我说的是性。是的，我知道。
I'm talking about sex. Yes, I realise that.
真是太棒了。
It was marvellous.
我忘记了。
I'd forgotten.
我可以很浪漫，但到了紧要关头，
I can be quite a romantic, when push comes to shove,
你爸可从没欣赏过这一点。你能不能别…?
not that your dad ever appreciated that. Oh, can you not just...?
怎么啦？嗯,这是……哦。我让你难堪了吗?
What? Well, it's... Oh. Have I embarrassed you?
我不需要知道。没事，没事。
I don't need to know. It's fine, it's fine.
不管你做什么，都很好，很好。你是成年人。这是……
Whatever you do, it's fine, it's good. You're adults. It's...
我以为你会为我高兴。
I thought you might be happy for me.
我是。我是!
I am. I am!
我爱你，你知道。
I love you, you know.
我知道你喜欢。
I know you do.
我打不通我们的吉莉安。
I can't get through to our Gillian.
她不接电话什么的。
She's not answering her mobile or anything.
我再给你倒点茶好吗?
Can I get you some more tea?
不,不。不，不，我没事。
No, no. No, no, I'm fine.
另一个鸡蛋吗?不,谢谢。
Another egg? No, thanks.
对不起，你说什么?
Sorry, what did you say?
关于吉莉安的事?
Something about Gillian?
好吧，去哪儿?
Right, where to?
我不能回家。
I can't go home.
我爸爸把我赶出去了，我妈妈说她再也不想见到我了。
My dad's chucked me out and my mam says she never wants to clap eyes on me again.
我不会把拉菲的房间给你的。
I'm not giving you Raffy's room.
喂?
Hello?
约翰?朱迪思。你想要什么?
John? It's Judith. What do you want?
呃…我,嗯…
Er... I, um...
你不应该打这个号码。如果是卡洛琳接的呢?
You shouldn't ring this number. What if Caroline had answered it?
她不是在上班吗?
Isn't she at work?
你想要什么?
What do you want?
你不能借给我一些钱，是吗?
You couldn't lend me some money, could you?
只是房东有点…和我不愉快
It's just that the landlord's getting... unpleasant with me
关于拖欠房租和…
about the rent arrears and...
你会因此受益。
You get benefits for that.
是的,是的。
Yeah, yeah.
问题是……
The thing is...
我已经花了。哦,耶稣。
I've spent it. Oh, Jesus.
你不希望我出现在你家门口，对吧?
And you don't want me turning up on your doorstep, do you?
我小时候肯定在这里待了好几个小时。
I must have spent hours in here when I was a kid.
是啊，我也是。
Yeah, so did I.
我一直试着…哄骗它
I always tried to, er... wangle it
这样我们就能坐在一个我可以凝视你的地方。
so that we'd sit somewhere where I could gaze at you.
你没有吗?你这篇愚蠢的文章。
You didn't? You daft article.
你是唯一让我能忍受的人。
You were the only thing that made it bearable.
我讨厌教堂。
I hated it, church.
我以前很无聊，很痛苦。
I used to get so bored and miserable.
是的,很好。
Yeah, well.
提醒你，这比他们现在的那些快乐的东西要好。
Mind you, it's better than all this happy-clappy stuff they have now.
毫米吗?你要薄荷糖吗?是吗?为什么?至少在开心的时候，
Mm? Do you want a mint? Is it? Why? At least with the happy-clappy stuff,
人们看起来真的很想待在那里。
people actually look like they want to be there.
这是不合适的，不是吗?
Well, it's not proper, is it?
现在葬礼上都有流行歌曲了。
They have pop songs at funerals now.
是吗?那又怎样?
Yeah? So what?
葬礼上的流行歌曲?
Pop songs at funerals?
当我们还是孩子的时候，宗教就是关于控制。
Religion when we were kids was all about control.
它讲的是统治阶级与教会的勾结
It was about the ruling classes being hand in glove with the Church
让那些勤劳的普通人害怕拥有自己的思想。
to keep the ordinary hard-working people terrified of having a mind of their own.
是地狱吗?!不，是的。
Was it hell?! No, it was.
你想想看。
You think about it.
我不想和你争论。
I won't get into a debate.
葬礼上为什么不能放首流行歌曲呢
Why shouldn't you have a pop song at a funeral
如果是你喜欢的东西，对你有意义的东西?
if it's something that you've liked, something that's meant something to you?
流行歌曲是给……迪斯科舞厅，酒吧和社交俱乐部。
Pop songs are for... for discos and pubs and social clubs.
在教堂里你唱赞美诗。
In church you sing hymns.
葬礼上的流行歌曲
Pop songs at funerals
都是普通民众用自己的方式庆祝，
are about ordinary folk celebrating whatever, in their own way,
不接受身居高位的人强加给他们的东西，
not accepting what's inflicted on them by people in high places,
他们只想让所有人都感到恐惧和痛苦。
who just want to keep everybody frightened and miserable.
嗯…
Well...
有些人需要身居高位的人时不时地告诉他们什么是什么。
some people need people in high places to tell them what's what now and again.
下次你要告诉我你投了玛格丽特·撒切尔的票。
You're going to tell me next you voted for Margaret Thatcher.
你不会喜欢迈克尔·富特吧?
Well, you can't have liked Michael Foot?
在纪念碑上穿夹克?
In his anorak at the Cenotaph?
一个非常聪明的人，迈克尔·富特。
A very intelligent man, Michael Foot.
他不可能有那么聪明
Oh, he can't have been that intelligent
不然他就不会像个稻草人一样到处走了。
or he wouldn't have gone around looking like a scarecrow.
我不讨厌托尼·布莱尔……哦!
I didn't dislike Tony Blair... Oh!
直到他在伊拉克把票弄脏了。
Until he muckied his ticket in Iraq.
现在，戈登·布朗，有一个饱受诟病的人。
Now, Gordon Brown, there's a much-maligned man.
英国首相戈登•布朗(Gordon Brown) ?毫米。
Gordon Brown? Mm.
想让每个人都喜欢他，用他虚伪的笑容?
Trying to get everybody to like him, with his phoney grin?
他是苏格兰人。
And he's Scottish.
现在，这是一个无懈可击的政治论点!
Now, there's an unassailable political argument!
不用说，他把经济搞得一团糟。
Well, it hardly needs pointing out he buggered up the economy.
不，他没有。
No, he didn't.
他没有。他有远见。
He did not. He had vision.
哦,上帝。我知道这是一个我们必须避免的话题。
Oh, God. I can see this is a subject we're going to have to avoid.
不，别担心，我会教你的。你绝对不会的。
No, don't worry, I'll teach you. You damn well won't.
我们会给你买份《卫报》
Yeah, we'll buy you a copy of the Guardian.
你可以保留你的守护者。
You can keep your Guardian.
我好像在你的回收箱里发现了一份《每日邮报》
I thought I spotted a Daily Mail lurking in your recycling bin.
《每日邮报》怎么了?有什么问题吗?
What's wrong with the Daily Mail? What's wrong with it?
它怎么了?
What's right with it?
你知道吗，我从没想过让你参加火热的工党。
Do you know, I'd never have had you down for red-hot Labour.
我以为你有更多的东西。
I thought you had more about you.
你知道大卫·卡梅伦的好处吗
Do you know, the good thing about David Cameron
连他自己都知道自己是个混蛋!
is that even he knows he's an arse!
不，每次他开口，你都能看到他在想，
No, every time he opens his mouth, you can see him thinking,
我生下来是个混蛋，死也会是个混蛋，但至少我知道我是个混蛋
"I was born an arse, I'll die an arse, but at least I know I'm an arse."
你突然变得很粗鲁了，巴特肖先生。
You've suddenly got very coarse, Mr Buttershaw.
那么，你结婚时穿的是什么呢?毫米吗?
So, what will you be walking down the aisle to, then? Mm?
耶路撒冷?统治不列颠?
Jerusalem? Rule Britannia?
示巴女王的到来。
The Arrival Of The Queen Of Sheba.
怎么啦？
What?
不，不，那是……
No, no, that's...
什么? !
What?!
这是非常合适的!
It's very appropriate!
嗯，我会去的。
Mm, I'd turn up for that.
我知道我得重新教育你了，艾伦·巴特肖。
I can see how I'm going to have to re-educate you, Alan Buttershaw.
这意味着我可以选择我们出去的音乐吗?
Does that mean I get to choose the music we walk out to?
地狱,没有。
Hell, no.
这已经非常明显了
It's become screamingly obvious
我不能再信任你了，就像我可以抛弃你一样。
I can't trust you any further than I could chuck you.
嘿。
Hey.
我忘了我们是在教堂。我们像骑警一样咒骂。
I forgot we're in church. We've been swearing like troopers.
好吧，那我们最好去找牧师。
Well, we'd better find t'vicar, then.
如果这是你想要的。
If this is what you want.
如果你觉得我在压迫大众，那就不是了。
Well, not if you think I'm oppressing the masses.
噢，压迫群众半个小时还是值得的
Oh, it'll be worth oppressing the masses for half an hour or so
看到你像示巴女王一样到来
to see you arriving like the Queen of Sheba.
我希望不是一个女人。
I hope it isn't a woman.
谁?
Who?
教区牧师。
The vicar.
如果你坚持周六的档位，那你就只能看四个……
If you're insisting on a Saturday slot, you're looking at four...
五个月后。
five months away.
我想宜早不宜迟。毫米。
I think sooner rather than later. Mm.
你们俩有谁离婚了吗?
Are either of you divorced?
不。不,不。
No. No, no.
丧偶的。
Widowed.
很明显你们俩都经常去教堂?
And you're both regular churchgoers, obviously?
好吧，我们过去是这样的。
Well, we have been in the past.
嗯。
Hm.
那么，你现在不经常去教堂了?
So, you're not regular churchgoers now?
不是……不。
Not... No.
你上次去教堂是什么时候?
When did you last go to church?
呃…圣诞节吗?
Er... Christmas?
19…噢,呃…
19...oh, er...
77年?
77?
你呢?
What about you,
道森太太吗?差不多一样。
Mrs Dawson? About the same.
毫米。
Mm.
那么，你为什么要上帝的祝福，
So, why do you want God's blessing,
如果你不去教堂?
if you don't go to church?
我只是感兴趣。
I'm just interested.
我们觉得他可能会喜欢这个交易。
We thought he might like the trade.
可怜的贱人!
Miserable bitch!
我是说，难怪人们不去。
I mean, no wonder folk don't go.
哦，我们可以住在灌木丛那边。
Oh, we could live over t'brush.
那你就不是巴特肖太太了。
Ah, but then you wouldn't be Mrs Buttershaw.
不，我想做个派对。我想买一顶帽子。
No, and I fancy having a do. I want to buy a hat.
我们可以再找一个牧师。我打赌他们不都是那样的。
Oh, we could find another vicar. I bet they're not all like that.
不，她让我失望了。就这样了，我和教会。结束的。
No, she's put me off. That's it, now, with me and the Church. End of.
晚安，维也纳。我已经离开大楼了。
Good night, Vienna. I've left the building.
那你想在哪结婚?
Well, where would you like to get wed?
因为，我是说，现在你可以在任何地方结婚。
Cos, I mean, you can get wed anywhere now, you know.
哦，某个高档的地方。
Oh, somewhere classy.
哦,是的。
Oh, yeah.
南奥拉姆大厅。
South Ouram Hall.
哦，我以前很喜欢南奥拉姆大厅。
Oh, I used to love South Ouram Hall.
它还在那儿吗?是的，就我所知是这样。
Is it still there? Yeah, yeah, far as I know.
他们没有搞砸吗?
They've not mucked it up?
不，我觉得还是和以前一样诡异。
No, I think it's just as creepy as it ever were.
他在这里做什么?这是我的房子。
What's he doing here? It's my house.
飞片。
Slapper.
是的,不管。
Yeah, whatever.
你是什么意思?这是什么?
What do you mean? Is this what...?
你和他?
You and him?
正确的。我要上楼去拿我剩下的东西。
Right. I'm off upstairs to get the rest of my stuff.
我就在外面。
I'll be outside.
你真的需要检查一下脑袋。
You really do need your head examined.
啊!啊!
Ah! Ah!
哦!哦!
Oh! Oh!
喂?商店吗?
Hello? Shop?
什么，没人吗?不，看起来不像。
What, nobody about? No, doesn't look like it.
喂?
Hello?
我表姐爱丽丝在这里见过一次鬼。
My cousin Alice saw a ghost here once.
在哪里?呃…楼上。
Where? Er... upstairs.
那是什么感觉?
What was it like?
一个女人。
A woman.
不要去。
Don't go.
我不能把他赶出去。他没有别的地方可去。
I can't chuck him out. He's got nowhere else to go.
我将……我去。你不能!你……你不能。
I'll... I'll go. You can't! You... You can't.
不喜欢。
Don't.
我…我想是这个房间。
I...I think it were this room.
呃…她从那扇门进来的。
Er... she came through that door.
她走过这里……
She walked across here...
然后穿过那堵墙消失了。
and disappeared through that wall.
哦。
Ooh.
我们走吧?
Shall we go?
停电。我们走吧。
Power cut. Let's go.
哦!
Oh!
喂?有人在吗?
Hello? Is anybody there?
喂?
Hello?
喂?电话。
Hello? Telephone.
我这儿没有信号。我也没有。
I've got no reception. Neither have I.
什么……
What the...
哦……不…
Oh... No...
你觉得有人发现我们失踪了吗?
Do you think anyone's realised that we're missing?
我只是担心我爸身上带着治疗心脏病的药。
I just worry about my dad having his pills on him for his heart.
上面有人。
There's somebody up there.
你怎么知道他没带她去酒店
How do you know he hasn't taken her to some hotel
为了一个疯狂的夜晚，互相推搡，眨眼?
for a wild night of nudge-nudge, wink-wink?
他们到底在哪儿?
Where the hell are they?
为什么车在那里，他们不在里面?你还得保持清醒足够长的时间
Why's the car there and them not in it? You still have to stay sober long enough
用白纸黑字写下来。尿了!你觉得他们死了吗?
to actually get it down in black and white. Piss off! Do you think they're dead?
你拿那个量尺干什么?你烧了我的路虎吗?
What were you doing with that dipstick? Did you torch my Land Rover?
我不会在你和别人乱搞的时候和你住在一起。你知道门在哪里。
I'm not living with you while you're having it off with someone else. Well, you know where the door is.
字幕 memoryonsmell http://UKsubtitles.ru.
Subtitles by MemoryOnSmells http://UKsubtitles.ru.